Welcome to the India Market Invest Mindset.  He
told those who are new to the channel to please
subscribe, like, and
press the bell icon.  Press the bottom all the way with it.
The notification will reach
you immediately.  RBI is
continuously boosting the banking sector or
financial services sector.
Liquidity has been released into the market.  As a result, you can
say that the banking sector is doing
well.  Along with that, the financial
sector is also doing well and the
demand for NBFC companies is continuously
increasing.  For this reason, NBFC companies are
continuously
racing upwards.  See NBFCs in demand
Bajaj Finance, Cholamdlam, LNT
Finance, each company but
continuously almost on a daily basis.
Hitting 52 week highs or hitting record highs.  If
you look at today too, you will see that
NBFC
companies, especially Bajaj Finance, have shown quite good movement.  4
percent showed a good upside movement.
Besides, the festival season is
underway.  So, during the festival season, people
need extra money.  So
these companies are fulfilling the demand for that money.  Due to
which business is growing and in
addition to that, each of these companies
also provides finance to the auto sector.
Where the demand for autos is also increasing.  This
festival season.  So naturally, the
business of NBFC companies is growing.  For this
reason, NBFC companies
have seen good movement today or
have been showing good movement for several days.  Dixon Technology is a
company that is doing quite well in the electronics segment, especially in the mobile, tablet, or computer segments,
and is now also
working in the semiconductor segment.  So this company
was showing continuous good performance.  So now there is
some bad news about this company.
Domestic broking house Philip Capital.
So Philip Capital says that Dixon Technology could
show a 47% downside movement.  And for this
reason, who is taking cell readings?  Philip
Capital.   There are
currently 16,000 somethings going on.  So what is the target for this
company, which is talking about a 47% downside movement
?
What to do now, sir, let me tell you that a
broking house is giving a target of 985. It does
not mean that the company will come to that place
immediately. You have to analyze
what the company does and whether there is
demand for the work it is doing or whether it is doing that
work properly or whether the company is
increasing its quarterly profitability or
increasing its revenue or such.
Then analyze it well and
think about the stock. Just because a broking house
is saying this does not mean that the
company will reach 9085 tomorrow or the day after tomorrow or in two or three
months.
What is the reason that FE earned 80% of its revenue in 25th
from whom?  Dixon
Technology from Motorola Company.  So
what is this brokerage house saying about the reason behind the 60% drop
?  It says that domestic demand is declining
and that Apple and other
Android phones are
flooding the market.  This is why
Phillips Capital says Dixon Technology could
see a downside movement of up to 47%.
Ola Electric Ola Electric has presented
a good movement of over 4% today.
So, there is
a big news about Ola Electric.
Let's see what news is
available.  Check out this article to see
Ola Electric.  This stock hit the upper circuit by about 5% today.
For what?  EV
scooter maker to launch first non-vocal product  This
means that the company is going to
diversify its business.
What is the name of this non-vehicle sales product?  Ola power.  Where is Ola Shakti
not going to launch a new product
?  In the energy sector.  The
company is set to launch this product in the energy sector on October 17th.
So this is why
an upper circuit of 5% has been observed within the company today.
ICICI Lombard.  So this company
has shown a good strong rally of 8% today.  What is the reason behind showing it?  Strong
quarter two results.   In
addition, the company has also
declared a dividend.  How much does an interim dividend make
?  How much is the share price of 6 taka pa paisa
and the company's record date?
November 12th.  The company reported that the
company's
net profit increased by 18% year-on-year.  And
besides that, the total income, which is the revenue, has
increased by 12.5%,
sir. How many sales were there in the September quarter, June
quarter and September quarter a year ago?
6147 A year ago, in the previous quarter,
6396 6869.
So, the annual quarterly revenue has increased,
and if you look at the expenses, you can see 5207 A year ago, in the
previous quarter, 5415 5822. So, the expenses have also
increased annually. If you take the
operating profit income minus expenses,
a year ago it was 940 in the previous
quarter, 981 in this quarter, 1044. So, the
operating profit, which can be
jumped annually and quarterly, and the net
profit, which can be seen after tax and adjustments, is
694 A year ago, in the previous
quarter, 747, in this quarter, 820. So, the
net profit has also jumped.  The
company has shown good performance,
but today the company has
presented a good movement of 89%. Lawson
& Toubro is a big large cap
company. The company
says that today it has hit a ton of monthly
highs
and along with that Jefferies has hiked the
target.  So
if you say the reason behind the good movement today, it is because
Jefferies has
given a bullish and buy rating to this company.
What did Target give?  Target 4345.
How much did Earlia target?  4,230.  So
from there, they increased the target.
So for this reason, a
good movement has been observed within the LNT.
Good news for the legal profession.  What is the good news?  Where
Anil Agarwal's provision is that this company
sought approval from CCI, i.e. the Competition Commission of India.
For what?  To Acquire Joy Procus
Associate.  To acquire this company.
So CCI, i.e. the Competition
Commission of India, gave him a signal.
So obviously this is
good news for Vidhanta or Anil Agalwal or for his shareholders.
Jio Financial Services is an NBFC
company.  The company that
has declared the date of its results.
Now you can say
that the results of this company will be very interesting.  Until now, there was
not much momentum in business.
But now the company has slowly
started business.  Where AMC's
business is called, banking business is called,
payment solution business is called, or
insurance business is called.  Besides that,
there is the loan business.  Say personal loan
, say mortgage loan.  So when is the company
going to announce its results?  Look, the company
has announced that
when it will report its second quarter earnings?  October 16th.
So for those who have GFS, that
is, do not have Jio Financial Services,
October 16th is
very important.  So you have to stay connected to the channel so that the
right information reaches you at the right time.
Disclaimer: Sir, I have only tried to present to you the
news available about the companies I discussed in this video.
So please do
n't take this video as a buy recommendation.
Before you buy, do a good analysis yourself.
Understand your own risk.  Then bye.
Because if your money sinks, it will
sink only you.  Thank you.  Be well.